{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"11.8.0","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":3570,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":29,"width":970,"height":535,"responsive":false,"scalable":false,"launchFile":"index.html","isVRProject":false},"contentStructure":[{"id":"SmartShape_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_1","title":"If the abandon code is “@Loc (A)”, press the F3 key and type IMPRD in the “Trans ID” field to verify the insert dimensions. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_13","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["IMPRD"]},"constraints":{"length":5}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_1","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_17","title":"Click the white box and type IMPRD. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_17","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide7911","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_1","Text_Entry_Box_13","Success_Shape_1","Hint_Shape_17","Failure_Shape_17"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7911"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_81","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_81","title":"Enter the Product number (84275002). Then, press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_47","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_47","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["84275002"]},"constraints":{"length":8}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_21","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_21","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_50","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_50","title":"Click the white box and type 84275002 then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_37","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_37","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide7944","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_81","Text_Entry_Box_47","Success_Shape_21","Hint_Shape_50","Failure_Shape_37"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7944"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_74","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_74","title":"To view the attributes of the Product (84275002), press Enter.  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_75","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_75","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_76","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_76","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_77","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_77","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_78","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_78","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_79","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_79","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_80","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_80","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_46","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_46","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["P"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_49","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_49","title":"Press the Enter key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide18133","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_74","SmartShape_75","SmartShape_76","SmartShape_77","SmartShape_78","SmartShape_79","SmartShape_80","Text_Entry_Box_46","Hint_Shape_49"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide18133"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_9","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_10","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_11","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_12","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_13","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_14","title":"To compare the current case cap in IMPRD to IIPAA, press F3. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_15","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["P"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_19","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_19","title":"Press the F3 key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8004","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_9","SmartShape_10","SmartShape_11","SmartShape_12","SmartShape_13","SmartShape_14","Text_Entry_Box_15","Hint_Shape_19"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8004"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_15","title":"To compare the current case cap in IMPRD to IIPAA, type IIPAA in the “Trans ID” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_16","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["IIPAA"]},"constraints":{"length":5}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_2","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_20","title":"Click the white box and type IIPAA. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_18","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8064","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_15","Text_Entry_Box_16","Success_Shape_2","Hint_Shape_20","Failure_Shape_18"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8064"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_16","title":"Enter the Product number (84275002). Then, press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_18","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["84275002"]},"constraints":{"length":8}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_4","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_22","title":"Click the white box and type 84275002 then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_20","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8097","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_16","Text_Entry_Box_18","Success_Shape_4","Hint_Shape_22","Failure_Shape_20"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8097"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_17","title":"View the IIPAA case cap. To get an insert with the recommended dimensions, press F3. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_18","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_19","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_19","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["P"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_23","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_23","title":"Press the F3 key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8157","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_17","SmartShape_18","Text_Entry_Box_19","Hint_Shape_23"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8157"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_19","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_19","title":"To get an insert with the recommended dimensions, type IIAVA in the “Trans ID” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_20","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["IIAVA"]},"constraints":{"length":5}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_5","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_24","title":"Click the white box and type IIAVA. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_21","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_21","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8217","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_19","Text_Entry_Box_20","Success_Shape_5","Hint_Shape_24","Failure_Shape_21"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8217"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_20","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_21","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_21","title":"Fill in the appropriate information: Category (S), From Location (X), To Location (6), Minimum Location Height (1). Then, press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_73","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_73","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_21","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_21","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["SX61"]},"constraints":{"length":4}}}},{"id":"Text_Animation_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Animation_5","roles":{}},{"id":"Success_Shape_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_6","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_25","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_25","title":"Click the white box and type SX61 then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_22","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8250","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_20","SmartShape_21","SmartShape_73","Text_Entry_Box_21","Success_Shape_6","Hint_Shape_25","Failure_Shape_22"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":180},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8250"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_23","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_23","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_22","title":"Browse the available locations that meet the recommended insert dimensions and the yearly bin trips (X61117E1). Then, press F3 to assign a new location to the part. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_22","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["P"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_26","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_26","title":"Press the F3 key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8283","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_23","SmartShape_22","Text_Entry_Box_22","Hint_Shape_26"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8283"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_24","title":"To assign a new location (X61117E1) to the part, type IIPAA in the “Trans ID” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_23","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_23","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["IIPAA"]},"constraints":{"length":5}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_7","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_27","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_27","title":"Click the white box and type IIPAA. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_23","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_23","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8343","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_24","Text_Entry_Box_23","Success_Shape_7","Hint_Shape_27","Failure_Shape_23"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8343"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_27","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_27","title":"In the “Add” screen, enter the Use code (P) and the C code (P) . Then, press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_28","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_28","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_24","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["PP"]},"constraints":{"length":2}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_8","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_28","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_28","title":"Click the white box and type PP then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_24","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8403","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_27","SmartShape_28","Text_Entry_Box_24","Success_Shape_8","Hint_Shape_28","Failure_Shape_24"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8403"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_29","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_29","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_30","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_30","title":"To enter the new location, type X61117E1 in the “Location” column field. Then, press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_25","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_25","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["X61117E1"]},"constraints":{"length":8}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_9","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_29","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_29","title":"Click the white box and type X61117E1 then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_25","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_25","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8436","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_29","SmartShape_30","Text_Entry_Box_25","Success_Shape_9","Hint_Shape_29","Failure_Shape_25"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8436"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_34","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_34","title":"To move the material to the new bin location, press F3. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_27","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_27","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["P"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_31","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_31","title":"Press the F3 key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8469","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_34","Text_Entry_Box_27","Hint_Shape_31"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8469"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_36","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_36","title":"To move the material to the new bin location, type ISPMH in the “Trans ID” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_28","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_28","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["ISPMH"]},"constraints":{"length":5}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_11","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_32","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_32","title":"Click the white box and type ISPMH. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_27","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_27","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8529","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_36","Text_Entry_Box_28","Success_Shape_11","Hint_Shape_32","Failure_Shape_27"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8529"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_37","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_37","title":"Enter the License Plate number (701563634) in the “LP” field, then press the Tab key to the “From Loc” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_29","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_29","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["701563634"]},"constraints":{"length":9}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_12","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_33","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_33","title":"Click the white box and type 701563634 then press Tab. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_28","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_28","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8562","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_37","Text_Entry_Box_29","Success_Shape_12","Hint_Shape_33","Failure_Shape_28"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8562"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_38","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_38","title":"Press the Tab key to the “To Loc” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_39","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_39","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_40","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_40","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_31","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_31","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["P"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_34","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_34","title":"Press the Tab key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8595","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_38","SmartShape_39","SmartShape_40","Text_Entry_Box_31","Hint_Shape_34"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8595"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_41","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_41","title":"Enter the Main Bin location (X61117E1) and press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_32","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_32","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["X61117E1"]},"constraints":{"length":8}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_13","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_35","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_35","title":"Click the white box and type X61117E1 then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_29","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_29","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide11781","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_41","Text_Entry_Box_32","Success_Shape_13","Hint_Shape_35","Failure_Shape_29"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide11781"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_42","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_42","title":"To choose the highlighted license plate and its quantity, press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_33","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_33","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["P"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_36","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_36","title":"Press the Enter key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8628","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_42","Text_Entry_Box_33","Hint_Shape_36"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8628"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_43","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_43","title":"Enter the quantity to move (54), then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_34","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_34","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["54"]},"constraints":{"length":2}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_14","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_37","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_37","title":"Click the white box and type 54 then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_30","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_30","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8688","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_43","Text_Entry_Box_34","Success_Shape_14","Hint_Shape_37","Failure_Shape_30"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8688"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_44","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_44","title":"Press Enter to assign the inventory to the new location. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_35","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_35","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["P"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_38","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_38","title":"Press the Enter key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8748","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_44","Text_Entry_Box_35","Hint_Shape_38"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8748"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_70","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_70","title":"Press N for “No” in response to the “Create RF work?” message. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_45","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_45","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["N"]},"constraints":{"length":1}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_71","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_71","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_72","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_72","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_20","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_48","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_48","title":"Click the white box and type N. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_36","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_36","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17920","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_70","Text_Entry_Box_45","SmartShape_71","SmartShape_72","Success_Shape_20","Hint_Shape_48","Failure_Shape_36"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17920"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_45","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_45","title":"Press the Esc key to exit the screen and return to the “DALLAS SYSTEM MENUS” screen. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_36","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_36","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["P"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_39","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_39","title":"Press the Esc key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8928","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_45","Text_Entry_Box_36","Hint_Shape_39"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8928"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_46","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_46","title":"Press the F3 key to open the “NAVIGATOR” screen. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_38","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_38","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["P"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_41","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_41","title":"Press the F3 key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8988","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_46","Text_Entry_Box_38","Hint_Shape_41"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8988"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_47","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_47","title":"To complete the abandon and the Pallet Move, type RMVUC in the “Trans ID” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_39","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_39","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["RMVUC"]},"constraints":{"length":5}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_15","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_42","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_42","title":"Click the white box and type RMVUC. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_31","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_31","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9048","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_47","Text_Entry_Box_39","Success_Shape_15","Hint_Shape_42","Failure_Shape_31"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9048"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_48","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_48","title":"Enter the license plate information (701563634), in the “License Plate” field. Then, press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_49","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_49","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_18","title":"Enter the license plate. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_40","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_40","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["701563634"]},"constraints":{"length":9}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_16","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_43","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_43","title":"Click the white box and type 701563634 then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_32","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_32","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9081","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_48","SmartShape_49","Text_Caption_18","Text_Entry_Box_40","Success_Shape_16","Hint_Shape_43","Failure_Shape_32"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9081"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_50","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_50","title":"To resolve the abandoned workunit, press the Tab key to navigate to the “Modify-dtl” screen. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_51","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_51","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_42","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_42","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["12609263"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_45","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_45","title":"Press the Tab key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9174","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_50","SmartShape_51","Text_Entry_Box_42","Hint_Shape_45"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9174"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_57","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_57","title":"To complete the Pallet Move, type C. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_58","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_58","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_59","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_59","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_60","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_60","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_19","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_19","title":"AVL ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_41","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_41","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["C"]},"constraints":{"length":1}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_17","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_44","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_44","title":"Click the white box and type C. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_33","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_33","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9237","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_57","SmartShape_58","SmartShape_59","SmartShape_60","Text_Caption_19","Text_Entry_Box_41","Success_Shape_17","Hint_Shape_44","Failure_Shape_33"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9237"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_67","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_67","title":"You have completed this process. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_69","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_69","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide13624","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_67","SmartShape_69"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide13624"}}},{"id":"Pool423","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":423,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"@LocTraining","class":"project","title":"@LocTraining","children":["Slide7911","Slide7944","Slide18133","Slide8004","Slide8064","Slide8097","Slide8157","Slide8217","Slide8250","Slide8283","Slide8343","Slide8403","Slide8436","Slide8469","Slide8529","Slide8562","Slide8595","Slide11781","Slide8628","Slide8688","Slide8748","Slide17920","Slide8928","Slide8988","Slide9048","Slide9081","Slide9174","Slide9237","Slide13624"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":379,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":[],"minScore":0,"maxScore":0,"passScore":0}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"launch_content","SCCriteria":"launch_content","exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide7911","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide7944","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide18133","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide8004","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide8064","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide8097","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide8157","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide8217","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide8250","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide8283","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide8343","title":"Slide 11"},{"id":"Slide8403","title":"Slide 12"},{"id":"Slide8436","title":"Slide 13"},{"id":"Slide8469","title":"Slide 14"},{"id":"Slide8529","title":"Slide 15"},{"id":"Slide8562","title":"Slide 16"},{"id":"Slide8595","title":"Slide 17"},{"id":"Slide11781","title":"Slide 18"},{"id":"Slide8628","title":"Slide 19"},{"id":"Slide8688","title":"Slide 20"},{"id":"Slide8748","title":"Slide 21"},{"id":"Slide17920","title":"Slide 22"},{"id":"Slide8928","title":"Slide 23"},{"id":"Slide8988","title":"Slide 24"},{"id":"Slide9048","title":"Slide 25"},{"id":"Slide9081","title":"Slide 26"},{"id":"Slide9174","title":"Slide 27"},{"id":"Slide9237","title":"Slide 28"},{"id":"Slide13624","title":"Slide 29"}]}